Hello everyone and welcome back to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Kathryn and today we have a wild lesson for you at the elementary level.
我是Kathryn，今天我们为大家准备了一堂初级水平的精彩课程。
That's right.
没错。
We are actually going to visit a farm.
我们实际上要去参观一个农场。
So yeah, it's going to be fun.
所以，是的，会很有趣。
We're going to see a lot of animals.
我们会看到很多动物。
And not only that, but we're going to learn a lot of interesting words and phrases in
不仅如此，我们还会学到很多有趣的单词和短语，
English today.
今天用英语。
But before we get started, let's take a look at vocabulary preview.
但在开始之前，我们先来看看词汇预览。
Vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
Old MacDonald had a farm, ee-yah, ee-yah-oh.
老麦克唐纳有个农场，咿呀咿呀哦。
And on his farm he had a duck, ee-yah, ee-yah-oh.
他的农场里有只鸭子，咿呀咿呀哦。
We're not going to be teaching you this song today.
我们今天不会教你这首歌。
Don't worry.
别担心。
You don't have to listen to us sing.
你不用听我们唱歌。
We do have a great word to start us off.
我们有一个很棒的开场词。
It's called, the word is country.
这个词是“country”。
Okay, so you know country as like the United States.
好，你知道“country”可以指国家，比如美国。
Mexico.
墨西哥。
Mexico, China, etc.
墨西哥、中国等等。
But in this case, we are going out to the country.
但在这里，我们要去乡下。
Not out of the country, we're going out to the country.
不是出国，而是去乡下。
To the country, okay?
去乡下，明白吗？
The country, or you might hear, the countryside is a place that's not like a city.
“Country”或“countryside”指的是不像城市的地方。
So it's the opposite of city.
所以它是城市的反面。
It means there's lots of grass, it's very natural, there are very, very few houses and
这意味着那里有很多草地，非常自然，房子和人都很少，
people, it's very quiet.
很安静。
So it's the opposite of a busy city.
所以它是繁忙城市的反面。
It's the country.
就是乡下。
You have a lot of animals.
那里有很多动物。
So usually, farms are found on the countryside or at the countryside.
所以通常，农场都在乡下或乡村地区。
In the countryside.
在乡下。
So usually farms are found in the countryside.
所以通常农场都在乡下。
That's right.
没错。
And I personally am a big fan because it's so quiet and peaceful.
我个人很喜欢，因为那里非常安静平和。
Yeah, very good.
是的，很好。
We can talk about that in a minute.
我们可以稍后再聊这个。
Let's listen to today's dialogue first and then we'll be back to talk about some of the
我们先听今天的对话，然后回来讨论一些
words and phrases.
单词和短语。
Isn't this great?
这不是很棒吗？
I always wanted to own a farm, live out in the country, grow my own food.
我一直想拥有一个农场，住在乡下，自己种食物。
This is very beautiful.
这里真美。
Though I have to confess, I don't know the first thing about farming.
不过我得承认，我对种地一窍不通。
That's fine.
没关系。
Don't worry about it.
别担心。
What was that?
那是什么声音？
Relax.
放松点。
It was just a goat.
只是一只山羊。
And that?
那又是什么？
It's just the cows that are grazing over there.
只是那边在吃草的奶牛。
We can milk them later.
我们待会儿可以挤它们的奶。
What was that?
那是什么声音？
Honey, seriously.
亲爱的，说真的。
It's just a sheep.
只是一只羊。
Relax.
放松点。
That was just the horses and donkeys that are in the stable.
那只是马厩里的马和驴。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I don't think I can hack it out here in the countryside.
我觉得我受不了这乡下地方。
I'm going back to the city.
我要回城里去。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So obviously some people cannot go to the countryside.
所以显然有些人不能去乡下。
That's right.
没错。
Some people get very, very upset.
有些人会非常非常不安。
In fact, there was a whole TV show in America that was about city people living in the countryside.
事实上，美国有一整档电视节目就是关于城里人住在乡下的。
Let's see if they can do it, right?
看看他们能不能适应，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
All right, but before we talk about that, why don't we take a look at four key words
好，但在我们聊那个之前，不如先看看语言要点里的四个关键词。
in language takeaway.
语言要点。
Language takeaway.
The first word is the name of an animal.
第一个词是一种动物的名字。
Okay, so you've all heard of cows, but have you heard of goats?
好，你们都听说过奶牛，但你们听说过山羊吗？
A goat.
山羊。
All right, so a goat is a strange looking animal.
好，山羊是一种长相奇怪的动物。
It's kind of skinny.
它有点瘦。
What do you get from a goat?
你能从山羊身上得到什么？
You can actually drink goat's milk.
你可以喝羊奶。
Many people like to eat goat's cheese, which is cheese made from goat's milk.
很多人喜欢吃山羊奶酪，也就是用羊奶做的奶酪。
Okay, so a goat.
好的，所以是一只山羊。
We heard the sound that a goat makes, so I think it's pretty clear what a goat is.
我们听到了山羊发出的声音，所以我觉得山羊是什么很清楚。
They're very common, as we say, in farms, such as sheep and horses, cows, etc.
它们很常见，就像我们说的，在农场里，比如绵羊、马、牛等等。
That's right, and normally, when they're in the wild, they like to live in rocky places,
没错，通常它们在野外时，喜欢住在多岩石的地方，
like mountains.
比如山上。
Right, that's why they say they're very good climbers, because they don't fall off the
对，这就是为什么人们说它们是很棒的攀爬者，因为它们不会从山上掉下来。
mountains.
山上。
All right, and well, if you have cows, then they're probably going to be grazing.
好了，嗯，如果你有牛，那它们很可能在吃草。
Okay, so to graze is a verb.
好的，所以“graze”是一个动词。
It's something we do.
这是我们做的事情。
Well, we people don't do it.
嗯，我们人类不做这个。
Animals do it.
动物做这个。
It's a way for us to describe how animals, like cows, eat.
这是我们描述动物（比如牛）如何进食的一种方式。
Means to eat grass.
意思是吃草。
Okay, so if your cows or horses are grazing, that means they're eating grass somewhere
好的，所以如果你的牛或马在“grazing”，那意味着它们在某个地方吃草。
out.
外面。
That's right, they're walking, they stop, they eat some grass, they walk, they stop
没错，它们走着，停下来，吃些草，再走，再停下来。
again.
再停下来。
It's a very slow process.
这是一个很慢的过程。
All right, so cows are usually grazing out in the countryside, and well, once they finish
好了，所以牛通常在乡下吃草，嗯，等它们吃完草变胖后，早上你就得挤奶。
grazing and they get all fat, then in the mornings, you have to milk them.
挤奶。
Okay, so we drink milk.
好的，所以我们喝牛奶。
Milk is a thing, but it's also a verb.
牛奶是一个名词，但它也是一个动词。
So to milk something.
所以是“to milk something”。
All right, and if you milk a cow, is when you extract the milk, the liquid from them.
好了，如果你给牛挤奶，就是从它们身上提取牛奶这种液体。
That's right, so underneath a cow, there's an udder, or underneath a cow, there are udders,
没错，所以在牛下面有一个乳房，或者说牛下面有乳房，
which you have to squeeze with your hands to make the milk come out.
你得用手挤压才能让牛奶流出来。
Okay, an interesting word as well, udder.
好的，一个有趣的词，“udder”。
It's like that big bag full of milk.
就像那个装满牛奶的大袋子。
Exactly, so to milk a cow.
没错，所以是“to milk a cow”。
All right, and you have cows out in the fields grazing, and probably your horses and donkeys
好了，你有牛在田野里吃草，可能你的马和驴会在马厩里。
are going to be in the stable.
马厩里。
The stable is a place, okay, so this is something that's often found on farms, where the horses
马厩是一个地方，好的，这是农场里常见的东西，马或牛住在那里。
or the cows live.
牛住在那里。
It's a structure, it's a building for those animals.
它是一个结构，是给这些动物住的建筑。
Okay, so they're probably separated in different little rooms or compartments, and that's called
好的，所以它们可能被分隔在不同的房间或隔间里，这就叫马厩。
a stable.
马厩。
So as you say, you usually find horses and cows and donkeys in there.
所以就像你说的，你通常会在那里找到马、牛和驴。
That's right, so a stable is a way to protect animals from the weather.
没错，所以马厩是保护动物免受天气影响的一种方式。
All right, very good.
好了，非常好。
So four key words there as we just saw.
所以我们刚才看到了四个关键词。
Why don't we listen to this dialogue again, and we'll be back soon.
我们为什么不重新听一遍这段对话，我们很快回来。
Isn't this great?
这不是很棒吗？
I always wanted to own a farm, live out in the country, grow my own food.
我一直想拥有一个农场，住在乡下，自己种食物。
This is very beautiful, though I have to confess, I don't know the first thing about farming.
这很美，不过我承认，我对农耕一窍不通。
That's fine, don't worry about it.
没关系，别担心。
What was that?
那是什么声音？
Relax, it was just a goat.
放松，只是一只山羊。
And that?
那又是什么？
It's just the cows that are grazing over there.
只是那边在吃草的牛。
We can milk them later.
我们待会儿可以给它们挤奶。
What was that?
那是什么？
Honey, seriously, it's just a sheep.
亲爱的，说真的，只是一只羊。
Relax.
放松。
Relax, that was just the horses and donkeys that are in the stable.
放松，那只是马厩里的马和驴。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I don't think I can hack it out here in the countryside.
我觉得我受不了这乡下地方。
I'm going back to the city.
我要回城里去。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now let's take a look at Fluency Builder.
现在让我们看看“流利度构建器”。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建器。
You know, Marco, I have to confess.
你知道吗，Marco，我得承认。
I love Fluency Builder.
我喜欢流利度构建器。
All right, and that's our first phrase for today.
好了，这是我们今天的第一句话。
I have to confess.
我得承认。
Okay, so to confess is to tell someone something that's a secret.
好的，所以“confess”是告诉别人一个秘密。
So we can confess with a priest.
所以我们可以向神父忏悔。
So we can confess to a priest.
We can confess a secret to a friend.
我们可以向朋友坦白一个秘密。
But I have to confess is a very common phrase.
但“I have to confess”是一个非常常见的短语。
It's a way for us to start a sentence.
这是我们开始一句话的方式。
I have to confess.
我得承认。
So you're saying I have to be honest with you.
所以你在说，我必须对你诚实。
I have to tell you the truth.
我必须告诉你真相。
Exactly.
没错。
So I have to confess.
所以，我得承认。
I'm not a huge fan of that sweater.
我不是那件毛衣的超级粉丝。
So I have to be honest.
所以我得说实话。
I really don't like your sweater.
我真的不喜欢你的毛衣。
This is a way for us to be more polite when we're saying something that's negative.
这是我们在说负面话时更礼貌的一种方式。
And in this case, it was a girl who was confessing and what she confessed is her second key phrase.
在这个例子里，是一个女孩在坦白，而她坦白的内容是她的第二个关键短语。
I don't know the first thing about farming.
我对农活一窍不通。
Okay, so I don't know anything about farming.
好的，所以我对农活一无所知。
There's another way we could say this or I don't know a thing about farming.
我们还有另一种说法，或者“我对农活一窍不通”。
But I don't know the first thing about farming means I don't even understand what a farm
但“我对农活一窍不通”的意思是，我甚至不明白农场是什么，
is.
是什么。
Okay, the first thing is what is a farm?
好的，最基本的问题就是：农场是什么？
I don't even understand what a farm is for.
我甚至不明白农场是用来干什么的。
This is a way for us to say I don't know anything at all about this.
这是一种表达方式，用来表示我对这件事完全不了解。
And if we change the noun, right, and we can say for example, I don't know the first thing
如果我们换一下名词，对吧，我们可以说，比如，我对汽车
about cars.
一窍不通。
So I have no idea what models they are or what type of engine they have.
所以我完全不知道它们是什么型号，或者有什么类型的发动机。
I don't know the first thing about cars.
我对汽车一窍不通。
All I know is how to turn them on.
我只知道怎么发动它们。
Right.
对。
Or I don't know the first thing about wines.
或者我对葡萄酒一窍不通。
I'd love to learn about wine, but I don't know the first thing about it.
我很想学学葡萄酒，但我对它一窍不通。
Okay, so it's a phrase that you can use with many, many different nouns, right?
好的，所以这是一个你可以和很多很多不同名词一起使用的短语，对吧？
I don't know the first thing about architecture.
我对建筑一窍不通。
I don't know the first thing about English.
我对英语一窍不通。
Right, well, we do and that's why we're here to help you.
对，嗯，我们懂，这就是为什么我们在这里帮你。
But this is a really great phrase to describe not understanding anything at all about something.
但这真是一个很好的短语，用来描述对某事完全不了解。
Right.
对。
So this is a really great way to describe not knowing anything at all about something.
所以这真是一个很好的方式，来描述对某事完全不了解。
Okay, and well, obviously since she didn't know the first thing about farming, she ended
好的，嗯，显然，因为她对农活一窍不通，她最后
up leaving and she said, you know what?
离开了，她说，你知道吗？
I don't think I can hack it out here in the countryside.
我觉得我在乡下撑不下去。
Okay, so I can hack it, he can't hack it.
好的，所以“我能撑住”，“他撑不住”。
We use this with the verb to be able to and it means I don't think I can do this.
我们和动词“能够”一起用，意思是“我觉得我做不到这个”。
I think this is too hard.
我觉得这太难了。
Or maybe if somebody quit, right, after a week at the office and you can say he couldn't
或者如果有人辞职了，对吧，在办公室干了一周后，你可以说“他撑不
hack it.
住”。
He couldn't hack the pressure and he left.
他承受不了压力，就离开了。
Exactly.
正是。
So that means to handle or to be able to handle or to withstand.
所以那意思是处理、能够处理或承受。
So I just don't think I can hack the cold.
所以我只是觉得我受不了这寒冷。
Right, I can't handle the cold.
对，我受不了寒冷。
It's too cold here.
这里太冷了。
I'm moving somewhere warm.
我要搬到暖和的地方去。
All right, so I'm sure you guys will be able to hack our dialogue one last time.
好了，所以我肯定你们能最后一次撑住我们的对话。
So let's listen to it and we'll be back.
那我们再听一遍，然后回来。
Isn't this great?
这不是很棒吗？
I always wanted to own a farm, live out in the country, grow my own food.
我一直想拥有一个农场，住在乡下，自己种食物。
This is very beautiful, though I have to confess, I don't know the first thing about farming.
这很美，不过我不得不承认，我对农活一窍不通。
That's fine.
没关系。
Don't worry about it.
别担心。
What was that?
那是什么？
Relax.
放松。
It was just a goat.
只是一只山羊。
And that?
那又是什么？
It's just the cows that are grazing over there.
只是那边在吃草的奶牛。
We can milk them later.
我们待会儿可以挤它们的奶。
What was that?
那是什么？
Honey, seriously, it's just a sheep.
亲爱的，说真的，只是一只羊。
Relax.
放松。
That was just the horses and donkeys that are in the stable.
那只是马厩里的马和驴。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I don't think I can hack it out here in the countryside.
我觉得我在乡下撑不下去。
I'm going back to the city.
我要回城里去。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So as you said, you're a fan of the countryside and about farming, right?
所以就像你说的，你是乡下的粉丝，也喜欢农活，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
Well, I wish I knew more about farming.
嗯，我希望我对农活了解更多。
I don't know the first thing about milking a cow, but I do come from a part of the world
我对挤牛奶一窍不通，但我确实来自伊利诺伊州芝加哥附近的一个地方，
in Illinois near Chicago where we have a lot of farms and I appreciate the quiet and having
那里有很多农场，我很欣赏那种安静、有动物在身边、
animals around and being able to go on long walks without cars and horns and bicycles.
能远离汽车、喇叭和自行车去长途散步的感觉。
It is actually a little bit refreshing to be out in the countryside sometimes and not
有时候在乡下确实有点令人神清气爽，甚至没有
even have internet or cell phone coverage or anything.
网络或手机信号之类的东西。
So it's just basically you can't do anything else but relax, read a book, talk to people.
所以基本上你除了放松、读书、和人聊天，什么也做不了。
Now an interesting thing about this is a lot of people take for granted the countryside
关于这一点，有趣的是很多人把乡下视为理所当然，
because I've met many people who live in the city, who grew up in the city and have never
因为我遇到过很多住在城里、在城里长大的人，他们从未
seen, for example, a live chicken.
见过，比如，一只活鸡。
And when they see it, they just freak out and take pictures with the chicken or a cow
当他们看到时，就会大惊小怪，和鸡或牛
or something.
之类的东西拍照。
It's amazing.
太神奇了。
That's so funny.
真有趣。
That's really funny.
真的很有趣。
Well, I think it's very valuable.
嗯，我觉得这很有价值。
I think there are very valuable skills that you learn being out in the countryside like
我觉得在乡下能学到很多非常有价值的技能，比如
how to cook for yourself.
如何为自己做饭。
There's no one else who can cook for you or how to get food from animals.
没有其他人能为你做饭，或者如何从动物身上获取食物。
Or maybe you can't even use a microwave.
或者也许你连微波炉都不会用。
So how do you cook without a microwave or something?
那么没有微波炉之类的东西，你怎么做饭呢？
That's right.
没错。
And I think the biggest problem for city people when they come to the countryside is that
我认为城里人来到乡下时最大的问题是
it's dirtier.
这里更脏。
You know, you get mud and there are bugs.
你知道，你会碰到泥巴，还有虫子。
And I imagine some of our co-workers here having a very hard time in the countryside.
我想我们这里的一些同事在乡下会过得很艰难。
Yes, indeed.
是的，确实如此。
So why don't you guys come to our website EnglishPod.com.
那么你们为什么不来我们的网站 EnglishPod.com 呢？
Let us know what you think about this.
让我们知道你们对此的看法。
Maybe you're very familiar with the countryside or have a relative who's a farmer.
也许你对乡下很熟悉，或者有亲戚是农民。
It's great.
这很棒。
Visit us EnglishPod.com and if you have any questions or comments, you can leave them
访问我们的网站 EnglishPod.com，如果你有任何问题或评论，可以留在
there as well.
那里。
Can't wait to hear from you.
期待听到你的消息。
Happy studies.
学习愉快。
Bye everyone.
大家再见。
But now I'm confused how he 1999!
但现在我困惑他怎么是1999年！